pba.com 2004-06-02

# PBA Bowling Tour - Pro Sports League for Top American and International Bowlers

pba.com Privacy Policy

The Professional Bowlers Association ("PBA") recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of the PBA web site.

**Information Collected by the PBA Web Site**

In order to access certain portions of our web site, users must register and provide certain voluntary information about themselves. The PBA web site collects and stores information about its users: during users' registration for such features of the PBA web site; through users' participation in certain activities on PBA-related web sites, such as contests and polls; and through the use of "session cookies". A session cookie is a non-persistent cookie that is deleted from the computer's cache upon leaving a particular web site.

**Use of Information**

The PBA will not reveal to any third party a user's personal information provided to us through the PBA web site except in the following circumstances:

We have your permission or consent to share the information;

We need to share your information to provide the product or service you requested;

We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of the PBA to provide a product or service to you;

We are responding to subpoenas, court orders or other legal proceedings; or

We sell or acquire another business, or are acquired by another business, in which case such information may be one of the business assets transferred.

Using email addresses provided at registration or otherwise, the PBA periodically sends out email newsletters and promotional email to our users about services and products offered by the PBA, its affiliates and those entities advertising on our web site. Users can indicate that they do not wish to receive email from PBA, its affiliates or those entities advertising on our web site by completing and submitting the form at <http://www.pba.com/ubbcgi/Ultimate.cgi?action=intro>. Third parties will not contact our users through the use of our email newsletter lists except through advertisements within the newsletters themselves.

Our site uses session cookies to deliver content specific to users' interests and to honor their preferences. This information is used to assist us in creating a site that will serve the needs of our users.

Upon request, the PBA will remove users (and their information) from our database or permit them to "opt-out" of any further email contact from the PBA, its affiliates or those entities advertising on our web site. To request such removal, please complete and submit the form at <http://www.pba.com/ubbcgi/Ultimate.cgi?action=intro>.

**General**

The PBA is not responsible for the content or the privacy polices of web sites to which it may provide links or the web sites of those entities which advertise on our web site.

The PBA uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us by our users secure and to disclose such information only after obtaining permission from the user (except under the circumstances discussed above).

**Children**

The PBA web site does not sell products for purchase by children. Our products are only for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use the PBA web site only with the supervision of a parent or guardian. 

**Reviewing / Changing Your Information**

The PBA gives you the ability to edit your PBA web site account information and preferences at any time. Please visit the web page at <http://www.pba.com/ubbcgi/Ultimate.cgi?action=intro> to review and/or change your account information.

You may also request deletion of your PBA web site account by sending an email to [forums@pba.com](mailto:forums@pba.com). Please note that certain information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

**Security**

Your PBA web site account information is password-protected for your privacy and security.

**Terms of Use, Notices and Changes to Privacy Policy**

If you choose to visit the PBA web site, your visit and any dispute relating to privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the State of Washington. The PBA reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, the PBA web site and the terms, conditions and notices under which the PBA web site is offered. You are responsible for regularly reviewing these terms and conditions.
